what's up everyone
tiago league five here with a very
special video today
now we got a tree my mama earlier today
she went to a taco Bell and
and she got she got the almighty
the legendary something might give me
explosive diarrhea the the doritos
locos tacos I got
it yeah you know but i
do now
it also came with like a baja blast but
like as you can see I already drank that
i wasn't gonna wait
so like so right now I just got some
water to wash it down with
but this was a baja blast because you
know like if I go and taco Bell
you know I'm getting the good like
if you're going to taco Bell if you're
gonna have flying out of your ass
you want the baja blast
now I now I just gotta say
now I just
yeah I just gotta say when my mama went
she went to taco Bell at like
1pm in the afternoon it's like
it's like 3am the next day so
it's not going to be good but
look at that that's the good I can
smell that
wait did we get this open now
what I will say is I have never had a
doritos logo stalker before
i heard the and I also heard they
give you
but we'll we'll see we will all see
together
look at that
what the what the
is this
what the did somebody only eat some
of my food
look at that
look at that there's no dory that's a
burrito
that's a burrito and nachos
this is you know what this is somebody
oh i'll fill out hold on
the nachos are
you know just gonna hurry up and eat a
nacho
because
I'm hungry I'm hungry as a
i you know I think this is somebody's
trash
i don't know what happened
i might have to ask my mama back
you know what no I think I know what
when my mama
when my mama went taco Bell she did say
she wanted to take a so she left
my doritos locust taco
on the trash can ask you once you take a
massive smelly or something
maybe like she actually grabbed some
guys
some patrons like food or what's left of
it anyway
so what do you say
so what do you say we check out what
this burrito is all about
i don't know what my mom got me a
burrito when I told her I would have
doritos local sago
but you know what if sega didn't care if
you feel soccer around
why should I kill enough to get what i
want
okay
i think that was your taco Bell
you ain't that bad
I'm gonna go and tell
that I didn't get the doritos local taco
because you got some
five b and cheeseburgers and
taco Bell I see your ass
i see you
[Applause]
i think there was a rock in my burrito
i heard a crunch and that was
not cheese
what the
i mean it wasn't food this was
somebody's trash
i don't give a
you know what I know I told it I know
i said I was going to eat the dewey
smoker's taco
and I did until by that point I should
give it a 10 out of 10 but you know what
this is pretty good I can't
complain
so this is getting like a six or
some
that's what I'm talking about look at
that
oh yes I love that
you